

# **NGUYEN LE MINH KHOI**

Frontend Developer ReactJS, NodeJS

## PERSONAL PROFILE

Gender : Male

Birthday : 06/01/1983
Marital status : Married
Nationality : Vietnamese
Country : Vietnam

## **CAREER INFORMATION**

Level : Manager

Salary : 1.500 - 2.500 USD

Job type : Full time

Industry : IT - Software

Location : Ho Chi Minh - District 1

# **OBJECTIVES**

I graduated from University of Technology and study in higher diploma in software engineering. I have over 10 years experience in web application development, especially in frontend web development. I develop HTML / CSS / and javascript coding, making the site responsive and friendlier to smaller devices is one of my main aims as well as improving performance. Through the professional knowledge I have and with my experience, I will try to do the best job at the company. Constantly strive for yourself and become the core employee of the company in the coming time.

### **EXPERIENCE**

Year(s) of Experiment: 10

Current Level: Experienced (Non - Manager)

1/2022 - Now: .NET Developer - Công Ty TNHH Stepmedia Software Việt Nam

- Development website application using MVC, SQL Server on basic platform .NET CORE, C#...
- Frontend is using REACTJS, SASS...
- Company product development Deloitte, write new features reports, improve performance for APIs, troubleshooting to perfect products...

# 1/2018 - 9/2020 : Frontend Developer - CONEXUS VIET NAM - Full time

- Development website application using MVC, SQL Server on basic platform .NET 4.0, 4.5... And my specialize is develop UI with script, jquery, css...
- Programming vip 24, competence project. A candidate must pass a test presentation, after that, other counselor will evaluation depend on your test, and they will give some idea to help you find out an opportunity develop.
- moe project is a learning experience which aims to provide students with the opportunity to synthesise knowledge from various areas of learning, and critically and creatively apply it to real life situations. This process, which enhances students' knowledge and enables them to acquire skills like collaboration, communication and independent learning, prepares them for lifelong learning and the challenges ahead.

- Development website application using MVC, SQL Server on basic platform .NET 4.0, 4.5... And my specialize is develop UI with script, iquery, css...
- Programming vip 24, competence project. A candidate must pass a test presentation, after that, other counselor will evaluation depend on your test, and they will give some idea to help you find out an opportunity develop.
- moe project. Planner create course & learner join courses to study...

### 6/2011 - 11/2012: Developer - VIEN NAM SOFT WARE - Full time

- Programing projects websites for clients.
- Analysis, programming and development website application on the basic platform .NET 2.0, 3.5, 4.0... using ASP.NET, MVC, Entity Framework, Web services, html, jquery, css...

### 1/2008 - 1/2010: Technical support - FPT TELECOM - Full time

- Support clients about ADSL, LAN, WAN. Check client's connection on system, check information and all services assigned to clients.
- Support all problems that IT need to solve about Web server, mail server, FTP, IP static, NAT and troubleshoot IT's problems.
- Configure router.

#### **EDUCATION**

Highest Degree Level: College Completion date 8-2004

College - University of Technology

# **OTHER CERTIFICATES**

Higher diploma in software engineering FPT Aptech

10/08/2004 - Unlimited

SKILLS	LANGUAGES
--------	-----------

English - Advance

CSS

★★★★ jQuery

\* \* \* \* \* Responsive

★★★★ HTML

\*\*\*

Nodejs ★ ★ ★

FrontEnd

\* \* \* \*

ReactJs

\*\*\*